[engine revving loudly]
[Chrishell] Wow, this is so pretty.
-[Mary] Honey, I'm home.
-[women laughing]
Oh my gosh.
[Mary] That's where I would want to do
the ceremony.
-[Chrishell] Yes.
-[Mary] Right?
Yeah, on that beach.
[Mary] I've been having a terrible time
booking a wedding venue,
but this other agent, Shawn,
offered me a 35 million dollar
house in Malibu.
So if I get this, it's going to be epic.
Shawn?
[Shawn] I gotta call you back.
-Hi, Mary. Good to see you.
-Good to see you.
Oh. Mwah.
[Mary] So I brought reinforcements,
'cause we're making it be here.
-Thank you for having us.
-My pleasure.
[Mary] A lot of people in LA
have second homes.
The owners of this Malibu house
don't fully occupy it.
So Shawn is definitely doing me a favor
by talking to his clients
and getting this as my wedding venue.
Plus, they're willing to work
within my budget. Thank God.
It is such a weight off my shoulders.
-Oh.
-[Amanza] I just saw a dolphin.
-[Mary] Did you?
-Did you seriously?
[Mary] You said that,
that you see them sometimes.
-[Shawn] The wildlife here is crazy.
-Gorgeous.
Let me take you on a tour of this house,
I want you to see all of it.
[Shawn] This is the main living area.
This outside area, I mean,
you could have cocktail hour out here.
[Chrishell] Ooh, yeah, that'd be nice.
Girls, oh my god,
can you imagine?
[Mary] Everyone standing around like...
-[Shawn] Come this way.
-[Mary] Alright.
-[Amanza] It just keeps going.
-[Chrishell] I know.
-[Mary] There's so much potential.
-Oh, it wraps around.
[Shawn] How beautiful is this?
-[Mary] Yes.
-[Amanza] Wow.
[Mary] This would be such a gorgeous spot
for the reception, you're right.
[Shawn] A hundred percent,
and you have great neighbors.
You've got Flea
from Red Hot Chili Peppers.
Yeah?
[Shawn] Best of all,
you've got Lady Gaga up there.
I mean... I gotta take this call.
Enjoy the property a little bit.
I'll pick up with you guys
and show you the beach.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
The thing is, I wanted the destination
wedding so much and that's just like...
Logistically, it's not going to happen.
So this is like,
I feel like I'm on vacation right now.
-Exactly.
-Me too.
I think so, too.
That's exactly how ours was.
Because it was in Malibu,
it was like a destination
without it needing to be destination.
-[Amanza] I got married in Indiana and...
-[women laughing]
...it wasn't very romantic
that weekend, remember?
Oh my god!
I really do not want to talk
about Amanza's wedding.
Mary got food poisoning the night before.
She had eaten something sus in Indiana,
and she had to leave, like,
I think halfway through the reception.
She was like shitting
and throwing her brains out.
[chuckling]
Too bad we don't have something to cheers
your new wedding venue now.
We'll have to save it
for when you're getting hitched.
Yes, oh my god.
Now we just got to get your dress.
[Chrishell] The guest list,
how's that coming along?
I talked to Romain last night.
-He's still adamant.
-[Chrishell] He's not budging.
But I'm not gonna let
Davina come between us.
You know, we're getting married,
we're happy.
I just think, like, rip it off
like a Band-Aid and tell her
because it's going to make it
much better once you
just get that stress off your plate.
[Amanza] Couldn't she just come?
You wouldn't even see her,
this place is so big.
You could just stick her up
on one of the balconies,
and give her some binoculars.
Put her in time out over there.
Time out!
This fight with Davina is causing
so much strain on my relationship.
I cannot wait for this wedding to be over,
where I can just
settle down and and go back
to selling real estate.
♪ You chewed me up
Took me for granted ♪
♪ You couldn't see what I could do ♪
♪ I'm a fighter
And I'm feeling you ♪
♪ With some love to prove ♪
♪ Coming back, I'm giving back
And I'm stronger ♪
♪ No, I won't give in ♪
♪ So much confidence ♪
♪ Coming back... ♪
[Christine] I'm so excited
to show you this house.
-[man] Oh, yeah.
-[woman] Looks good.
[Christine] Hello!
[Chrishell] Hey, guys.
-Come on in.
-I want you to meet my clients.
-This is Max and Sepi.
-Hi, how are you. Pleasure to meet you.
Hi, I'm Max. Nice to meet you.
[Christine] They've been looking
for a family-friendly home.
I hope this is the one.
[Chrishell] Okay, this house is
just under 6,400 square feet,
so there's lots of space.
[Chrishell] Huge master,
lots of bedrooms, five in total.
-And you have a yard.
-Yes!
-Amazing.
-Great.
Look around, let her know
if you have any questions.
-Awesome, thank you.
-Absolutely.
[gasps] Gorgeous house.
-I know, it's really pretty, right?
-[Christine] A house of this size,
it's so hard to come by.
-[Sepi] Nice guest bedroom.
-Mm-hmm.
The only thing I'm worried about
is the levels with small kids.
[Sepi] We'd have to put a gate
for the kids.
-Yeah.
-[dog barks]
Oh, and the dog barking.
I noticed that.
Can you imagine losing a deal
because of that?
I've lost deals 'cause of stupider shit.
[Christine laughing]
I can't believe I might miss out
on selling this house
because of the neighbor's dog,
it won't stop barking.
-[dog barking]
-[Christine] So, what did you guys think?
You love it?
[Max] It's cool. Decent size, too.
Do you guys want to see the outside
where you'd be laying with the kids?
Let me show you.
[Sepi] See how much green we have.
[Christine] Look at the view, Max.
-[Christine] That's perfect for you.
-[Max] There you go.
The Valley views is...
That's like comparing... [laughing]
...Coors Light to Dom Pérignon,
it's just like... It's totally different.
[Chrishell] Artificial grass,
so you don't have to worry,
it's always going to look perfect.
[Christine] I love that.
You've got these pockets completely open
so you've got the indoor-outdoor feel.
This could be an extension
of your living room basically.
[Max] It's really nice.
Thank you so much for showing us.
-Sure, thank you for coming.
-Nice to meet you.
[Max] Thank you for your time.
-[Chrishell] Thank you guys.
-You guys love it?
I love it for you.
Honestly, I really really really do.
I think it's great.
I haven't been getting as many calls
on this house as I expected.
So, I'm really hoping that Christine's
clients are going to think it's perfect
because, honestly, I do think
it'd be really perfect for them.
[Christine] I feel like
they liked the house.
-I know, that's exciting.
-I think they liked it.
This is the first property
I've showed them that
they were like,
"Oh my god, it has a yard."
That's exciting.
Fingers crossed,
I really want to sell this now.
I mean, can you believe us
working together after last year?
-We have to make this happen.
-That would be amazing.
I'm not gonna lie.
Chrishell and I definitely started off
on the wrong foot,
but her and I are headed
in the right direction.
We both can respect
the value of a dollar.
-For sure!
-The value of a check cashing.
I mean, speaking of checks cashing,
I am like out of my mind trying to plan
the engagement party and everything.
I'm so stressed.
-My gosh, what are you doing?
-I'm not, my party planner's stressed.
Someone's stressed. I don't know.
Somewhere down the line,
someone's stressed about something.
I didn't plan mine
'cause I feel like it's too stressful.
I feel like the stressful part
is finding the guy,
throwing the party for the guy
should be the fun part.
So I think you should delegate it
to someone else to do.
That's why I feel bad for Mary
because she's so stressed out.
I know, she's planning
everything on her own.
Well, it's gotta be tough, because
it's obviously super expensive
and it's probably stress on both of them,
and I think that's why
Romain is so sensitive
about Davina coming
because she made that comment
about her paying for everything.
I did not see that coming.
-I didn't know he had that in him.
-No, I didn't.
Like, no way.
I don't want Davina to come to my wedding.
It's done.
[Chrishell] He's always
just so happy-go-lucky.
-What are you doing?
-[imitating Romain] "No!"
Watch someone come in
while you're doing this.
-She doesn't come with the house.
-"Davina not coming to my wedding."
[Christine] I was like, "What?"
Me and Maya are like, "What'd you say?"
"Davina!"
We're like, "What is he talking about?"
Oh my God.
[Chrishell] Do you even know
what you're gonna do?
So in my mind, picture like
Britney Spears's "Boys" music video.
Okay.
With the LED lights and the table
and the zebras...
-Okay.
-Anyway, I wanna do it like that.
Are you going to have any kind
of zebra skin at your... Please do not.
-What are you talking about?
-You always have furs.
You can't have a zebra
and also have zebra skin.
The zebras are just hanging out.
I feel like you're the kind of person
that would feed chicken to a chicken.
[both laughing]
-Tell me I'm wrong.
-The zebra got paid though.
Oh my God.
He took the check to Bank of America.
I don't think a zebra really wants...
He has a checking and savings account,
a Roth IRA and a CD.
Okay? That zebra is rolling
in the dough, literally.
Christian doesn't have any idea
what I'm spending on this.
Did he give you any kind of guidelines?
Just, "Put it on the tab." There you go.
[Christine] Christian likes
to buy me gifts, that's his thing.
So it works out perfect. [laughing]
[Christine] We don't really talk
about money,
but if I want something,
I have been known to go in his wallet,
get out his American Express,
click to take a picture,
send it to the salesperson.
He has some alerts on his phone.
So I have my Louis Vuitton
representative on speed dial,
so when he's sleeping...
I'll have her buy a purse
and then I'll delete the notification
while he's sleeping. [laughing]
I don't know, some call it fraud,
I call it love.
Whatever. [laughing]
Well, I'm sure it'll be beautiful.
So, you're gonna come, right?
It'll be really fun.
I'm actually... okay.
So I'm glad we get the chance to talk.
I did want to talk to you about this.
I love that you and I've gotten to where
we can work together and we can
maybe have a shared client together
and, you know, it not be so awkward.
But...
I just feel like it's inappropriate
for me to be there
and I just, respectfully will decline
because it feels too soon for me.
You and I, only last week,
could be in the same room together.
I don't want it to be awkward.
But then don't you feel like
that's being awkward by not accepting?
I'm cool with being friends with you
with a wall up,
but something like that is like
letting you in again and it scares me.
Well, I'm obviously shocked.
I didn't really realize we were on so...
like, different pages.
I mean, obviously my feelings
are hurt, but...
[Chrishell] I don't want your feelings
to be hurt, that's not my goal.
It just seems disingenuous and...
Disingenuous? By me inviting you?
No. For me going.
-Okay.
-It'd be better to have it this way,
than to be at an engagement party with
a couple I've never hung out with once.
He's gonna be like,
"Who's this bitch? The bitch you
told me about that you hate?"
And I'm like, "Hey, congratulations!"
I don't hate anyone.
Okay, I hate a few people,
but I don't hate you.
-Okay, but you did. Let's be honest.
-[Christine laughing]
-No.
-And so did I. Let's own it.
Okay.
And we only just got past that,
so, I'm just saying like...
Eh, baby steps.
[Mary] My clients bought this property
as a flip.
It was bank-owned, they rebuilt it,
and now I'm selling it for him.
And now my newest client Chris
is looking for an investment property
to rent out,
and I think this could be perfect for him.
Hi, how are you?
I didn't even hear you come in.
-Good to see you.
-Good to see you as well.
[Chris] Beautiful pool, my gosh.
-[Mary] Yeah, so this is it.
-It's amazing.
New construction,
and they just completely remodeled it.
Took it down to the studs.
So everything is new.
I'm going to take you
into the master first.
-[Chris] The fireplace is amazing.
-Yeah.
I like how every room leads outdoors.
-And super private.
-Exactly.
Every bedroom, no one can see in.
It's just very private.
It's one story, which is
the main thing you're looking for.
Hey, Mary?
Oh, Jason?
-Hi, Mary.
-[Mary] Hi.
Sorry, I'm just gonna show her around,
I know you're busy.
-Okay.
-You guys have met.
[Mary] Hi.
-Good to see you.
-I didn't know you guys were coming.
-Yeah, sorry.
-Nice to see you.
-Thanks for letting us check it out.
-Of course.
We don't want to interrupt.
-I'm just gonna show her around.
-[Chris] Thank you.
[Mary] Um...
-Sorry, I didn't know that was happening.
-[Chris] No worries at all.
[Chris] No worries.
I can't believe Jason
is crashing my showing.
I'm told they did just under
a million dollars in renovation.
I saw it when they bought it.
It was just a piece of shit.
So it looks like they did
a million dollars of work.
[Jason] So, it's a 500 square-foot
guest apartment.
and 2,500 square feet up here.
They added the pool, too.
The pool wasn't even here,
or the spa before.
-Alright, we'll switch.
-[Mary] Okay. [laughing]
-You guys get at that end.
-[Jason] Alright.
[Jason] Mary's asking 3.199 right now.
So, 3.2 million.
-Yeah, it ruins--
-Fits the style of the home.
Yeah, it ruins the look, it blocks...
They paid 1.7.
Probably spent a couple hundred thousand
in carrying costs over the last two years.
I think they spent a million
just on remodel.
So, right around three
is where they're into it.
I cannot focus with Jason here.
All I keep hearing is his voice.
I keep focusing on them.
I can't pay attention to my own client.
Mary, sorry to interrupt, guys.
Four bedrooms, three in the main house,
the fourth is the guest apartment.
-[Mary] That's correct.
-Right? Okay.
They're interested in leasing it out,
it'd be an investment for them.
What do you think
a monthly long-term rental would be?
I think furnished long-term,
it would be about 15,000 a month.
-Okay.
-Alright.
He's actually looking
for the same thing as well.
Exactly.
I think it rents for about 3,500 a month,
so I don't think your numbers
are gonna run.
[Chris] Oh, darn. [laughing]
-Alright, guys.
-Thanks, Mary.
[Mary] He's pretty savvy,
he'll do his own numbers.
-Thanks for that though, Jay. Good advice.
-You got it.
As long as we get a great interest rate...
And a good price.
We also have to negotiate...
[Mary] If you're looking
for an investment...
Even though I own the brokerage,
I'm also an active real estate agent.
It gets complicated.
Technically, I'm on both sides
of the transaction
and I want to represent
my agent's interests
and my client's interests.
Those are actually
long-term clients of Jason's.
They're legit, so if you're interested
we should probably get an offer in.
-[Chris] Alright.
-Good seeing you.
-You too.
-I'll give you a call later.
You know what I want to pay.
-[Jason laughing] Alright.
-[Amel] Bye.
-[Mary] Well, that was surprising.
-Sorry--
Yeah, sorry to barge in.
I've been telling her about this house.
She was really clear with me on pricing.
-She thinks it's a little overpriced.
-It's not overpriced.
It's a great location, but it is right on
the street and the yard's a little small.
Everything on Sunset Plaza
is on the street.
Oh, come on.
I'm just telling you that Amel is not
gonna write an offer you'll be happy with.
If she even writes.
So if you don't want to take it,
don't take it.
Okay, well, I'm not going to be
concerned about it
until I get something
offensive in writing, but...
It's not gonna be offensive.
If there's not a three in front of it,
it's pretty offensive.
If it's 2.999, then it's not...
It's not gonna be 2.9999999 either.
It's totally embarrassing to take an offer
under three million to my client.
Not just for me, but for the company.
-When it's my seller--
-It's my job to represent her, not you.
I'm not going to advise them
to take under market value. Why?
-If we write an offer--
-You deal with your client and I mine.
Don't stress me out anymore.
I'm at my wit's end.
This wedding is costing me so much money.
We have to fly our families in,
try to get hotels.
I'm doing everything I can.
-[Mary sighs]
-What about that house on the beach?
It's wonderful and it'll work,
but there's still everything else.
Romain just doesn't get it.
I'm working so hard--
Don't yell at me, yell at Romain.
I do.
It's just hard. I know it's important.
I want him happy.
I want his parents happy.
I want like...
I don't want to be mean, I don't want to
make him feel
like I don't want to marry him.
I do, a thousand percent.
All this wedding-relationship talk...
I think I'm getting a rash
or something like that.
Oh my god.
Oh... There is actually, yeah.
You should go to the doctor.
[Brett] Development properties are more
complicated than properties already built.
It's a lot of pressure because I help
the developer buy the property.
I run the numbers with them first
and say,
"You'll make money if you do this."
I'm involved throughout
the entire process.
The funds come from the developer.
If they don't make money, it's on me.
-[Maya] Wow.
-[Brett] Yeah.
[Maya] Don't go down. I have a son.
[Brett] It doesn't matter if I die
because I'm single?
It's still dirt, but it looks
so much different than last time.
[Brett] Well, it's been a year.
[Maya] How many square feet
is the basement?
-6,500 square feet.
-Wow.
14 ft deep.
One of the biggest basements
built in Hollywood Hills.
I can't believe that.
When do you think it'll be ready?
[Brett] 16 more months.
[Maya] How often
can they dig the dirt out?
[Brett] One week a month,
they let us take dirt out.
Three weeks we're sitting on our ass.
What do you do with the dirt?
Where do you take it? To Jason's house?
-Jason's yard, yeah.
-[Maya laughing]
Remember what you told me
last time you were here?
Yeah, by the way I'm pregnant.
I'm kidding, no.
You told me that last time.
I know, last time.
Will I crack the joke that
I'm pregnant again? Not yet.
Hopefully soon.
What's crazy is you've had a baby
since the last time we were here.
All we've done is dig a hole.
I was busy.
How long does it take to permit
something like this?
I would say, with all the structural work,
I'd say at least one and a half years,
two years?
-[Brett] A year.
-Yeah.
If you're good.
What do you call it when it's completely
ready to go? Shovel ready?
-RTI.
-Yes, RTI.
-Damn, I'm good!
-Ready to issue.
See, I was doing something
while I was pregnant.
I'm learning and I'm reading.
We should head down there.
You're in sneakers.
Brett, if you want to hike with me,
you can take me to Runyon Canyon.
-Shit!
-This is... Whoa!
I can't break an ankle, I'm a mom,
I have responsibilities.
-Wow.
-So, you're inside a basement.
Now I really see the size of it. Huge!
There's gonna be a huge tree right here
and you'll be able to see all the way up.
I'd love to be able to sell a huge hole
in the ground for 25 million, but...
-It's gonna be tough.
-I don't think I'm that good.
I like that you're so into this,
that you're learning so much.
-I like to get down and dirty.
-Yeah.
[Maya] I've been working really hard
to understand deeply
the development process.
It's a different transaction.
And I like it because
you can make a lot of money.
-Very productive day.
-[Brett] Woo!
So yeah, maybe I'll co-list now with you.
What do you think?
This one's my baby.
-You have so many babies, Brett.
-I do, I have a lot.
I do want to get you involved,
so we'll talk about that in the future.
I'm a little disappointed.
Brett takes me to this tour,
and I'm hoping maybe he's going
to put me as a co-list with him.
He was just rubbing it in my face.
"Look at this property.
Once I sell it, I'm going to make
a million dollars commission."
I'm like, "Come on, Brett."
This is my first solo,
my listing, open house.
I got this listing through Jason.
And it's really important that I sell it
because I have two little kids to feed.
I have a family.
[grunts]
Shoot!
Argh!
Okay, we're gonna pretend that works.
[Mary] I'm so excited to see Amanza
in action at her first open house.
And Jason may have asked me
to check in on her.
-Hey.
-[Amanza] Hi!
-[Amanza] Are you house shopping?
-I am.
You are? Will you buy this one from me?
Well, tell me about it.
-Do you have an agent?
-[both laughing]
It's nice to see a friendly face. I really
appreciate that Mary's here to support me.
-Hello, how's it going?
-How are you?
-Amanza.
-Hi.
-Charlie, nice to meet you.
-Nice to see you, Charlie.
Hi, I'm Amanza's colleague.
-Great to meet you.
-I just stopped in to check on her.
Just to say hi.
Do you live in the area?
-I do.
-Currently? You do?
Yeah, new to LA.
Okay, are you looking to buy?
Or just curious to see
what's for sale in the neighborhood?
Looking to buy.
[Amanza] What are you looking for?
Do you know square footage?
What's your budget?
Definitely need a pool, so check.
Have a look around.
If you have any questions,
-I'm here.
-Thank you.
Sorry, excuse me.
So, what's the square footage?
And when was this built?
[Amanza] That's a good question.
How long has it been on the market?
Um, I don't know.
[Amanza] I was studying this
before you walked in the door.
Are you giving everyone
those set of sheets when they come in?
Yeah... at some point.
How many bedrooms is it?
It's three bedrooms, three baths.
Here, I'll give you a sheet.
Just seeing all these people face-to-face
is giving me, like, massive anxiety. Um...
My mind is going blank.
I just, I never had
to do this as a stager.
[Mary whispers] You're doing great.
[quietly] Thank you, I'm sweating.
[woman] I've known you forever
so I'm so happy to hear that.
-Oh!
-Hi!
[Mary] What are you doing here?
There's so many people.
-Good to see you.
-Are you doing what I'm doing?
Yeah, it's a little bit misleading.
[woman] I did not expect all of this
when I walked in.
I was gonna say...
Hi! Who's this?
-[man] This is Alexa.
-[Amanza] Hi, Alexa.
-Say, "Hi."
-How are you today?
Are you helping Daddy look for a house?
-[man] Yes.
-Yeah?
She'll be good with these buyers
'cause she's so good with kids.
-Let me grab you a sheet on the house.
-Okay.
It took me a minute, but I do learn.
[chuckling]
[man] What do we have here?
-This is so nice out here.
-[man] Wow, it's beautiful.
It's peaceful.
You've got the outdoor dining.
Do you want to see the fish?
There's fish
-in the water here.
-Do you want to go with her?
Come here.
Okay.
[Amanza laughing]
I would like to have my wife
come and look at this.
Yeah, for sure.
And maybe if you have a card or something,
I can contact you.
-Well, thank you so much.
-Thank you.
-See you soon.
-Bye, Alexa.
She's like such a mama bear.
I know.
That's so cute
[Amanza] How cute was that little girl?
[Chrishell] So cute.
-She was adorable.
-The cutest.
I kinda wanted to kidnap her.
That might have been a little awkward.
Honestly, it's a great house,
it's a great location.
-[Amanza] I'd buy it.
-It's priced really well.
I don't think you're going to have
an issue selling the house.
[Mary] You're doing really well, hon.
I just wanted to tell you,
we've been watching...
How are you feeling?
With everything that went down.
You feeling good with Heather?
It terrifies me how fast
you have met those kids.
I'm glad you're worried about
my boyfriend's children, thank you.
If I thought that you were going to be
this angry at me for saying it,
-I would have kept my mouth shut.
-Good.
Oh. [scoffs]
Because I know you guys
needed to talk it out.
-So it felt like it went well.
-I guess, I don't know.
I felt that day like it was fine.
But...
I've so many other major life things
going on that I honestly...
[Mary] Everything okay?
I'll sit here.
What's wrong?
[Amanza] Like, about the kids.
I don't know what it is, but I feel
like I'm gonna maybe have to...
Um...
Like, get full custody of them.
Oh my God.
At this point, legally we still have
50-50, but I don't know where he is,
so I need to be able to make decisions
without his signature, his approval,
because it's impossible right now.
So, I have a court date set
in a couple of weeks.
[chuckles awkwardly]
What happened?
I mean, he's not doing anything
bad to them, but it's...
I'm just like, you know.
My kids are like my world
and if they're not okay,
Mommy's not okay.
Yesterday, they just didn't seem
like they were okay.
Noah was sad.
-Honey, you've been going through so much.
-[Amanza] It's okay, I know.
Right now, I'm a little bit overwhelmed.
If you need any help,
I'm obviously here.
You love to babysit.
Did you just hear her say,
"I'll babysit anytime. I love kids."
[Mary] Okay.
[dragonfly buzzing]
[dragonflies buzzing]
What the fuck?
Oh my God! What is that?
-Look out behind you!
-[Mary yells]
[Chrishell] Oh my god, that scared me.
What was that?
It's a dragonfly, I think, right?
Maybe dragonflies are good luck?
No, it's if a bird shits on you,
it's good luck.
I think both.
Let's take it as a good sign.
-[Mary] I like that.
-Get the heck out of here.
-[phone ringing]
-[Mary] Hello?
Shawn Elliot, how are you?
I'm good. How are you?
[Shawn sighs] Unfortunately,
the owners of Il Pelicano
are in the midst of a divorce.
I guess the wife was all for the wedding
and the husband's not on the same page.
So, I'm really sorry to tell you
that, uh...
-[Mary] Oh my God.
-...you'll have to look for another venue.
Thank you for letting me know.
-[Shawn] Of course.
-[Mary] Okay, bye.
Okay, but...
Think about it this way,
we can find another spot.
-[Amanza] We just said that.
-Are you kidding me?
[Amanza] Okay.
My wedding's in five weeks.
♪ We're gonna do this
Like, like we do this ♪
♪ Ain't nobody else can do this ♪
♪ Like us, like us ♪
Hey Laura, it's Brett Oppenheim.
A quick question for you.
I'm looking at the pictures of your-- Oh!
Gosh, it's the wrong building,
never mind. I was gonna ask...
See it's not my building, Jesus.
[Jason] I didn't say it was.
-[Brett] Never mind.
-I'm tired.
Everyday I wake up at 5:30 a.m.
because Aiden is waking up.
[Heather] That's how I feel
being a stepmom, honestly.
A mom's job is hard. [laughing]
Yeah, it's a lot. I mean...
Yeah. I mean, I love it though.
I love it. It's just, um...
It doesn't stop. It doesn't stop.
[Maya] No, it doesn't.
Yeah, talk to me when you're
running on one hour's sleep,
holding a crying baby,
and you're covered with spit.
Talk to me then.
It's just making me realize,
I don't think I want my own.
[Maya] Really?
If anyone gets anything off market
in Santa Monica,
-around three, send it to me.
-[Heather] Where in Santa Monica?
It all sells pocket listing.
Anytime, let me know.
[Heather] I'm so out of the loop.
I can't even hear what's going on.
I'm not going to say anything then.
[cell phone ringing]
Christine, why are you FaceTiming me?
I'm FaceTiming you because I can't talk
to you, you're all the way back there.
It's the only way I can talk. Answer.
[Heather] Oh, hi.
[Christine] Listen. I have a buyer
who's looking for something
below 2.5 up in the Hills.
You guys, this is for you guys, too.
[Heather] He wants up to 2.5?
Up to 2.5, 2.7 maybe.
I just wanted to relay
that information to you.
-Thank you, babe.
-Okay, keep me posted.
-Okay, bye.
-[Heather] Bye.
So, let me know, guys.
I'm looking for a buyer.
[Amanza] Mary! Hi.
-[Brett] Did Frederick's team get back?
-[Jason] No, they're at Burning Man.
[Amanza] What's going on?
Kill me. Oh my God.
Guys, what's going on?
-The wife is still, um...
-[Heather] I'm coming.
[Heather] What's going on?
Our wedding venue fell through.
[Mary] The Malibu house.
[Maya] Really? Why?
The owners are getting a divorce.
-I thought it was set.
-[Mary sighs]
-What's your other options?
-[Mary] I have no idea.
I don't know what to do
because our family members
have booked their flights.
-They did?
-Are you serious?
Yeah, from France.
Do you have other back-up places?
-[Maya] The office.
-We're reaching back out.
What, we have five weeks?
Less than that.
I'm torn between pushing it back
and being like,
"why are we doing this?"
Romain and I are fighting all the time.
I would rather... not do it.
-[Chrishell] Oh, don't...
-[Amanza] Don't cry.
Mary, I think Christine said she'll do
a joint wedding with you.
You guys can get married together.
You're at 5 p.m. and she's at 7 p.m.
There you go.
[Amanza] I wanna get married, too.
-[Maya] Two birds with one.
-You can always get married at Jason's.
[Maya] I think Romain would rather
get married at my apartment.
There's no consummating
the marriage at my house.
-[Amanza] Ew, creepy.
-[Mary] I hate that word, consummating.
Sounds like constipated.
-I have that problem, too.
-[Jason] You know what we can do?
-We have a, uh...
-[women talking at once]
-One at a time.
-God, I know.
[Heather] Do a big...
-Do a restaurant, rent a big room.
-[Chrishell] Big reception party?
Hey, Lizzie.
I was wondering if you had any thoughts
on Mary's wedding venue. Question mark.
Lizzie is Mary's client, but Mary
often brings me on to her listings.
So I've gotten to know Lizzie very well.
I thought it would be a good idea just
to kind of put the bug in Lizzie's ear
and see if she'd be open
to Mary getting married there.
[Chrishell] I feel we should
just rent a yacht
and do it on a boat.
I know. Who's got a yacht?
-I like this idea.
-Jason, you know somebody with a yacht.
Just buy a yacht.
Yachts are like the worst investment ever.
I'm off of boats.
Get a hotel or like a restaurant or...
[Heather] Disneyland! Right?
[dogs whimpering]
-[Maya] What about the office?
-[Christine] Oh, God!
-[women speaking at once]
-Oh... Mary, hold on.
Hey, h-hold on...
Ten seconds here.
Ladies, phone call. I gotta... Can you?
[to himself] Oh fuck.
Hi, Lizzie.
Spend the money on a party.
[Jason] Hold on, I'm gonna walk outside
'cause it's hard to hear.
[Jason] I will walk outside of my
own office so I can actually work.
-[Christine] Bye.
-[Jason] Alright, go ahead.
Maybe it won't be a problem with
Davina because we'll all get uninvited.
[Christine] I'm noticing a trend.
[Mary] They just don't really get it.
Sorry. Mary, this is Lizzie,
on your ten million dollar listing.
Hi, Lizzie.
Hi, how are you?
-Good, thanks. How are you?
-I'm doing well.
[Lizzie] I talked to Jason
about the wedding.
-[Mary] No way.
-[Jason] Yeah.
[Lizzie] I know you love the house,
I'd be happy to offer it up to you.
[Christine gasps]
The side yard is a great place for
a ceremony, the back yard is beautiful.
[Mary] Lizzie, you have no idea how I...
Thank you.
It's my favorite home in the Hills
by far, and it would be
a perfect wedding venue.
Ah!
[both laughing]
I'm so excited.
[Jason] Alright, we'll talk about it.
I think this is awesome.
-I'm so excited.
-Yay, it worked out.
-I can't believe this.
-We'll be back
in touch later today. Thanks, Lizzie.
-[Jason] Alright.
-[Mary] Okay. Bye.
Bye.
-Woo!
-[Maya] What happened?
-You got it!
-Thank you, Jason.
-You're welcome.
-[Maya] Why are we clapping?
She got a place to get married.
My new listing.
-Right there, on Doheny.
-Doheny?
[Heather] The one that I saw?
I can't hear...
Heather, FaceTime, I can't hear you.
-[Christine] Mary found a wedding venue.
-What?
♪ It's time to throw it down ♪
♪ Let's give 'em sonething to talk about ♪
♪ Something to talk about ♪
[Christine] Oh my God.
-[woman] Smoking, per usual.
-Thank you.
[zebra whimpering]
Do you think that she went all out?
Of course, it's Christine.
-[Heather] Wow!
-Oh my God.
What is happening?
This party is so Christine.
It's crazy, it's sexy
and obviously way over-the-top.
I got to sit for one second,
my feet are killing me.
-Have you worn these yet?
-No.
-These are like stripper shoes.
-I know, thank you, right?
Come sit down, bitches.
[Christine] Finally!
I'm so tired of talking
about everyone else's issues,
now we can focus on me.
Cheers, ladies.
-Thank you, I'm so excited.
-So fun.
I love that there's a casual zebra
behind you.
I wouldn't expect anything less
at a party for you.
[Christine laughing]
Oh my God.
[Heather] What is she gonna have?
Something fun.
Christine, this was
delivered for you today.
How beautiful.
-Oh my gosh.
-Isn't it gorgeous?
This is stunning.
-Oh my goodness.
-Oh, wait.
"Christine and Christian,
I'm so happy for both of you.
I wish you nothing but the best.
May your life be filled with love
and happiness. XOXO, Chrishell."
Aw!
That's a nice move.
At first, my feelings were really hurt
she didn't come, I'm not gonna lie.
I didn't know she wasn't.
-Oh yeah, she's not coming.
-Why?
She declined me. She Heismaned me.
I'm sorry, what?
-[Heather] Why?
-She feels like
it would be disingenuous if she came.
I think she's put up this wall
against like...
What, the Great Wall of fucking China?
Yeah, I'm aware.
Now you gotta chop through that wall.
It's nice that she sent flowers.
It's been a lot of drama lately
in the office, I'm like...
Drama or not...
-Hey.
-[Mary] There's a zebra.
[Christine] Hi there. How are you?
[Christine] Hi, guys!
-Hey.
-You look amazing.
[Christina] Hi, sissy.
Don't be scared of the zebra.
Hi... Oh my gosh.
-Hi, Mary. How are you?
-How are you?
Good, I like your dress. It's cute.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Happy engagement.
[Heather] You're gonna get married!
Yes!
Some surprises going on, guys.
-This is totally Christine.
-I know.
[Christian laughing]
[guests talking, yelling]
Hi!
I never get to wear this so I'm like,
"Oh, red and black party?"
Thank you, guys. "Done."
-Where's the champagne?
-Oh my God, the red and black shoes.
[Maya] I don't eat meat.
[Maya] I'm Presbytarian? Pescatarian?
[Davina] No, Presbytarian is a religion.
[Maya] It is?
You know when you
don't eat meat, only fish?
-Pescatarian.
-But she was saying Presbytarian.
[Davina] I was like, that's a religion.
That is so fucking Maya, right there.
Hi, you look beautiful!
We both got the stash memo.
You look amazing.
So, I got here early with Davina.
Chrishell sent flowers.
At least Christine invited her
so that was a nice gesture.
And Chrishell sent flowers
as another nice gesture.
Baby steps.
Yeah.
Romain is still set with Davina?
Oh, we get in fights
almost everyday about it.
-[Davina] I have to say something...
-[Maya] You got to.
I mean, because everybody else
knows, you know?
It makes me want to throw up.
Like, to do it.
You know, Mary, it puts us in a tough
position to not say anything to her.
Maybe you should, I mean, tell her
about the situation and...
[Maya] I'm sure she will understand.
-I think it has to be sooner than later--
-[Mary] I know.
I've been putting it off
thinking I can change his mind.
-There's never gonna be a right moment.
-[Mary] Yeah.
-You just have to do it. It's like...
-Or an easy moment.
I don't think this is
the right moment, right?
It's Christine's engagement party.
I feel like Mary is making excuses.
She needs to talk to Davina now.
I'm just worried someone
will say something.
I don't want to say anything, but...
-I'm gonna go get another drink.
-Go get a drink.
Because I'm gonna have like a...
meltdown.
I would normally never do this
at Christine's engagement party,
but maybe Maya and Heather are right.
I just need to rip the Band-Aid off.
This whole situation is giving me
a heart attack.
-[Mary] Hey.
-[Davina] Hi! You wanna sit?
-No. Can I talk to you for one sec?
-Yeah.
Sorry, sorry.
Listen, I feel absolutely
horrible about this,
and I've been trying everything I can
to not have to do this. Um...
But Romain is, like, being adamant
that he doesn't want you
to come to the wedding.
Mm-hmm.
I feel horrible.
Um...
But he's so hurt...
by some of the comments
-that you made before.
-Mm-hmm.
And then, this is like...
[crying] I feel fucking horrible.
You know what? Christine told me.
And I'm just sad that
you went and told all our friends--
I didn't tell them.
Romain did, but that's still...
That's why--
It sucks, you know?
I look like a clown asshole.
-No, you don't. That's why I'm like--
-Everybody knew!
Every single person except me knows.
That sucks, Mary.
[Mary] I am actually pretty shocked.
I have no idea...
why Christine would do this.
I'm confused.
I'm hurt and I'm angry.
[chuckles] I'm... I'm really angry.
He had some drinks and he was saying...
I don't feel like you would do that to me.
[Mary sighs] There are some things
where I don't agree with certain things,
but at the end of the day,
I'm so sorry,
but I have to stick with my man.
-I'm marrying him, I have to.
-Of course.
I just wish you wouldn't
disrespect me like that.
Like he wouldn't, you know what I mean?
I don't know that I did.
[Davina] So, is Chrishell
coming to the wedding?
-Yes.
-Chrishell's coming to the wedding?
Okay. It just kinda sucks that
I'm being singled out, you know?
Part of it is because he works
so fucking hard.
He's the hardest worker I've ever met.
For people to think he doesn't work,
-he's mooching off my money.
-I didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
-He doesn't buy me a real diamond...
He's just like,
"Fuck you guys." He's mad.
I'm very direct and maybe
some of the things I said you don't like--
I think they come off wrong and harsh.
Alright... I know. You know what?
I think it's getting to the point...
It's Christine's party.
And I think we should talk
about this later.
-Right.
-Let's try to get you and Romain talking
at another time.
-Let's let them have their moment. Okay?
-Let's do it.
-Alright.
-[Christine] Guys!
Can we stop taking photos?
-We'd like to make a toast.
-Not an Instagram photo session.
-This is our engagement party.
-It is if you'd like it to be.
[Chrstine] We're so happy to be sharing
this moment with you guys.
-[Davina] Hmm?
-[Maya] Are you okay?
[Davina] I am.
I'm not the one who has a problem.
I love you guys so much
and I'm so excited that I get to have
the best life with the love of my life,
with my friends and my family.
We love you guys and thank you for coming.
-And Christian, I love you so much.
-Love you too, sweetie.
Let's see. Christine, I met you in
Beverly Hills last... not even a year ago.
And I absolutely fell head over heels
in love with you.
We had a dinner, she was wearing this
red dress and we hit it off in the car.
-We were literally in the car...
-Red dresses. That's how you get men.
We had, like, instant banter.
Which is really special,
you don't get that too often.
And I pursued her,
and she's a tough catch.
Uh, but...
Here we are now.
She's amazing.
She compliments me perfectly.
We're building an amazing life together.
I love you so much.
[Christine] Oh, thank you. I love you.
Cheers for Christine and Christian!
Cheers!
-[Maya] Christine and Christian.
-Cheers!
-Love you.
-Love you, too.
[Romain] Season... Game one.
[Jason] Fucking Barcelona.
It's the easiest team to like.
[Davina] Excuse me, gentlemen.
Could I talk to Mr. Romain?
Yeah, please.
-[Brett] Go ahead.
-[Davina laughing] Thank you.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-How are you?
-Good, and you?
Good.
So, um... obviously I heard that
you don't want me at your wedding
and Mary kind of explained to me
how you feel a little,
but I wanted to talk to you directly.
Because if your feelings are hurt
and you feel offended by me,
I wanna know that.
The point is, it's not even
like telling you, yet...
Yeah, I could have told you.
-The point is whatever you said--
-Well, it is.
-Whatever you--
-Because it's humiliating.
First of all,
the whole entire office knows.
And it puts our...
Forget about my feelings,
it puts all of our friends
in a bad position.
-[Romain] Is Mary your friend?
-Yes.
Okay, so when I got her a ring,
it doesn't fucking matter what I got.
-It could have been a rubber band...
-Wait, rewind.
When you said, "I'd have nothing
than a fake diamond..."
I wanna hear what you're saying, Romain.
I just think,
if you call Mary your friend,
you should never have a comment like that.
-That's fucking bullshit.
-Okay.
-If it's fucking bullshit...
-Yeah, it is.
...then why did you get a real diamond,
if it's bullshit?
I told her when I gave her the ring,
I say, "You deserve a diamond and
at some point I will get you a diamond,
the right ring you deserve."
And then what happened, I can afford it--
Do you think it was
a sensitive situation for you,
and maybe you took it
a little bit too serious?
-You're full of shit.
-Okay.
Alright.
I didn't know he was
this fucking hypersensitive.
To get in my face, a year later,
be this fired up. If you know
that what I said is wrong,
why is it piercing at you so much?
So, Chrishell made a comment
about a prenup.
-Yeah.
-And that's fine?
Yeah, and you... So, when Chrishell
asked you a question about us,
she knew us,
or at least she knew Mary, right?
If you're really her friend, then you know
she doesn't spend a cent for me.
Every time we go out,
I pay everything for both of us.
When you say to Chrishell, "Oh, yes,
she's paying everything for him,
and I hope she makes a prenup,"
that's fucking bullshit.
If you don't know the person,
you shut the fuck up and you don't
make any comment like that, okay?
Let's just be clear. Now we're good.
Wow.
Okay.
[Mary] Oh, you're still alive.
Is Davina alive?
I don't know.